fliqz.com 2008-05-12

# Privacy: Fliqz - We power video

Fliqz, Inc. ("Fliqz") values the privacy of our users, members, and others who use www.fliqz.com and any other web sites or services owned or operated by Fliqz (the "Fliqz Sites") (collectively or individually, "Users"). 

This Privacy Notice is incorporated into and is subject to the Fliqz  Terms of Use. Your use of the Fliqz Sites and any personal information you provide on the Fliqz Sites remains subject to the terms of this Privacy Notice and our Terms of Use. 

Please note that any video, image, blog entry, or other content posted at the direction of Users onto the Fliqz Sites becomes publicly-available content, is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Notice, and may be collected and used by others.

NOTE TO KIDS: THE FLIQZ SITES ARE NOT FOR PERSONS UNDER THE AGE OF 13\. _If you are under 13 years of age, please visit another site - there are lots of other great web sites for you._

_The Information Fliqz Collects:_

  * User Provided Information: You may provide to Fliqz what is generally called "personally identifiable" information (such as your name and email address) when you choose to participate in the various activities offered on the Fliqz Sites such as uploading videos, posting messages and blogging, reviewing and rating videos, entering surveys and contests, and subscribing to newsletters.
  * "Cookies" Information: When you visit the Fliqz Sites, we may send one or more cookies - a small text file containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer. Fliqz uses both session cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie disappears after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Fliqz Sites. Persistent cookies can be removed, but each web browser is a little different, so please look through your browser "Help" file to learn the correct way to modify your cookies set-up.
  * "Automatically Collected" Information: When you visit the Fliqz Sites or open one of our HTML emails, we may automatically record certain information from your web browser by using different types of technology, including "clear gifs" or "web beacons". This "automatically collected" information may include your Internet Protocol address ("IP Address"), web browser type, the web pages or sites that you visit just before or just after the Fliqz Sites, the pages you view on our site, and the dates and times that you visit the Fliqz Sites. 

_The Way Fliqz Uses Information:_

  1. Fliqz uses the information that we collect to operate, maintain, enhance, and provide to you all of the features and services found on the Fliqz Sites. We will use your email address, without further consent, for administrative purposes such as notifying you of major Fliqz Sites updates, for customer service, or to contact you regarding a video that you have posted.
  2. Fliqz uses all of the information that we collect to understand the usage trends and preferences of our Users, to improve the way the Fliqz Sites work and look, and to create new features and functionality.
  3. Fliqz uses "automatically collected" information and "cookies" information to: (a) remember your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit the Fliqz Sites; (b) provide custom, personalized advertisements, content, and information; (c) monitor the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns; (d) monitor aggregate usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages viewed; and (e) track your entries, submissions, and status in any promotions, sweepstakes, and contests that we might host.
  4. Fliqz will not use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send promotional or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in. 

_When Fliqz Discloses Information:_

  * **Fliqz does not share your personally identifiable information with other organizations for their _marketing_ or _promotional_ uses without your express consent.**
  * To provide web site hosting, maintenance and security, fulfill orders, offer certain functionality, improve our site, and to create new site features, we may disclose User information to affiliated companies or other businesses or persons. We require that these parties process such information in compliance with this Privacy Notice, we authorize only a limited use of such information, and we require these parties to use appropriate confidentiality measures.
  * Fliqz may share automatically collected and other aggregate non-personally-identifiable information with interested third parties to assist them in understanding the usage patterns for certain content, services, advertisements, promotions, and/or functionality on the Fliqz Sites.
  * Fliqz may disclose User information if required to do so by law, or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright law) or respond to a court order, judicial or other government subpoena, or warrant. We may make such disclosures without providing Users notice, in some cases.
  * Fliqz reserves the right to disclose User information that is necessary to enforce our Terms of Use; take precautions against liability; protect Users from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses; to investigate and defend ourselves against third-party claims or allegations; to assist government enforcement agencies; to protect the security or integrity of the Fliqz Sites; and to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Fliqz, our members, or others. 

_Your Choices:_

You may, of course, decline to share personally identifiable information with Fliqz, in which case you will not be able to upload videos or media to the Fliqz Sites. You may update, correct, or delete your member information and email subscription preferences at any time by going to the account section of the Fliqz Sites. 

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you account access or making corrections. YOU ARE RESPONSIBLE FOR MAINTAINING THE SECRECY OF YOUR UNIQUE PASSWORD AND ACCOUNT INFORMATION AT ALL TIMES. 

_Third-party Advertisers, Links to Other Sites:_

Fliqz allows other companies, called third-party ad servers or ad networks, to serve advertisements within the Fliqz Sites. These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to send, directly to your browser, the advertisements and links that appear on the Fliqz Sites. They automatically receive your IP Address when this happens. They may also use other technologies (such as cookies, javascript, or web beacons) to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and to personalize their advertising content. 

Fliqz does not provide any personally identifiable information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent or except as part of a specific program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in. However, please note that if an advertiser asks Fliqz to show an advertisement to a certain audience or audience segment and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience they were trying to reach.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers or ad networks. Fliqz's Privacy Notice does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

 _Our Commitment to Data Security:_

Fliqz uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical safeguards to preserve the integrity and security of your personal information. We cannot, however, ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Fliqz and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission of information, Fliqz makes commercially reasonable efforts to ensure the security of our systems. However, please note that this is not a guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. 

If Fliqz learns of a security systems breach, then we may attempt to notify you electronically so that you can take appropriate protective steps. Fliqz may post a notice on the Fliqz Sites if a security breach occurs. Depending on where you live, you may have a legal right to receive notice of a security breach in writing. To receive a free written notice of a security breach you should notify us at [privacy@fliqz.com](mailto:privacy@fliqz.com "Privacy"). 

_Our Commitment to Children's Privacy:_

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Fliqz does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information on the Fliqz Sites from persons under 13 years of age, and no part of our website is directed to persons under 13. IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE, THEN PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS THE FLIQZ SITES AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER. If Fliqz learns that personally identifiable information of persons less than 13 years of age has been collected on Fliqz without verifiable parental consent, then Fliqz will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. 

_Special Note to International Users:_

The Fliqz Sites are hosted in the United States and are only intended for and directed to Users in the United States. If you are a User accessing the Fliqz Sites from the European Union, Asia, or any other region with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, that differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your continued use of the Fliqz Sites, which are governed by U.S. law, this Privacy Notice, and our Terms of Use, you are transferring your personal information to the United States and you consent to that transfer.

_In the Event of Merger or Sale:_

In the event that Fliqz is acquired by or merged with a third-party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information we have collected from Users as part of such merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control.

_Changes and Updates to this Privacy Notice:_

This Privacy Notice may be revised periodically without further notice to you and this will be reflected by the "last modified" notice below. Please revisit this page to stay aware of any changes. In general, we only use your personal information in the manner described in the Privacy Notice in effect when we received that personal information. Your continued use of the Fliqz Sites constitutes your agreement to this Privacy Notice and any future revisions.

For revisions to this Privacy Notice that may be materially less restrictive on our use or disclosure of personal information you have provided to us, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you and obtain your consent before implementing such revisions with respect to such information.

_Effective Date, Date Last Modified:_

This Privacy Notice is effective as of March 27, 2006.

_Fliqz Contact Information:_

Please contact Fliqz with any questions or comments about this Privacy Notice, your personal information, our third-party disclosure practices, or your consent choices at [privacy@fliqz.com](mailto:privacy@fliqz.com). We will respond to your inquiry within 30 days of its receipt.  

If you would like to learn more about Fliqz or other Fliqz video solutions for your site, please contact our [sales team](mailto:websales@fliqz.com) or call 1-888-32FLIQZ (1-888-323-5479).
